When skies are turned for monochrome
And now, here are your results from the 25th Annual Penno Festival's
Game Performance Competition!
In third place, Shinjo High School!
Next up, the surprise hit of the contest!
In second place, Rise in High School!
And the school that receives first place for the stage portion is...
As expected, the strong performance of Woundozu Girls Academy
brings home the gold!
The beautiful and wild songstress with a temperamental nature.
Why does she hold people in such complete contempt?
No one knows her true desires, hidden behind that perfect smile.
SCREMING
Thank you.
Isn't that right?
Oh, you don't need to feel apprehensive though.
I'll most definitely be taking care of you all properly.
First place?
We won, really?
In the food booth portion, Rise and High's main cafe received an incredible number of votes, helping them win from behind at the eleventh hour.
It's way simple. Miku cranked up the pressure big time during the stage performance part. However, Rindouji's true worth usually lies in their food booth's excellent ultra hotties per capita ratio, which unfortunately was completely neglected this year.
Shio!
Well, duh. Of course we're winners.
Agreed. They never stood a chance against us.
We won!
We really won!
You've got to be kidding me. It doesn't make sense. There's no way they're actually serious about this. Don't you know?
I'm Miku Iza, you fools! Understand? Don't they understand?
Miku...
Just stop. My song won first place. I was supposed to win!
Look, the reason that we won may sound corny, but it has to do with that dependent on friends thing.
What do you mean?
Simple. I could never beat you with my singing. And so, the other students at Ryzen worked extra hard to help cover for my shortcomings. Which means the humans you arrogantly look down on can defeat you when they come together as a team. Come with us. Don't be alone.
Shut your mouth. Friendship? Teamwork? Give me a break. I've got news for you.
You face me, and those platitudes become meaningless.
Get out!
Miku! Wait! Listen to me, please!
look.
Sink! S Singing! Sink!
S cultivation...
Sailing...
No! Did you? Miku! You can't do this! Please!
They were your friends, weren't they? So darn reliable. So earnestly committed.
And so easily bent to my will.
Let me go!
I don't even care about the stupid promise anymore.
Because I will have my way and there's nothing in this world that can stop me.
Now then, you know what I want.
Sweet Shiori, the spirits. Everyone, you are all my personal property.
What? Hmm?
What did I just touch?
No.
You can't be. Come chuck underneath this one's skirt!
No!
Oof-oo-oo.
Oof-ooha.
Oof-o-ooh!
Oof-ooha!
Oh aah!
Oof!
Oof-ooha!
That's so gross!
Wait! Miku, please!
Just calm down!
Oof-oohh!
how dare you you tried to fool me the goal to play with my feelings crap where can i go
nowhere my only option is to stop miku
that's dangerous you can't hurt her anymore i won't let you yoshino not you too
you idiot did you really think we'd disobey our mistress's commands scornful we won't let you
lay a finger on her so forget it that's a spot of bad luck for you little shiori i can't believe
you brought so many spirits here with you plus there are all the types of girls that i like
no way not you too toka not you too
shito what in the world is going on here
toka you're not hypnotized huh i can barely hear you at all oh
your in-ear monitors wait you left them in yep i couldn't pick up the rhythm very well with only
one so what's going on well miku is pretty much in control of everybody kotori yes what's the
situation things have gone downhill in a hurry we're headed outside please bring frax and us to pick
us up huh what are you saying if you're dumb enough to go against our mistress then you should
stay and get torn to shreds but what the hell
you dare to trick miss miku death will be your atonement he's right drop dead where you stand
what's going on hey you're not affected are you well i was analyzing the sound on stage
everyone suddenly started acting weird basic realizers parallel driving force
replenishing magic power now preparing the converging magic power cannon
mistletoe target target savior square central stage commander why is it powering up because i'm
planning to evaporate anyone who might oppose my mistress miku in one fell swoop but you can't
vice commander help me stop her i'll ask you not to interfere i can't let this end i have finally
found my utopia you mean you're not under her mind control
hmm now all i have to do is push this button don't do it
anyone want to tell me what's going on here and start from the top i've been asleep for a while
not so hot now shame there isn't more time to really work you over but there are more important
things to do so let's put an end in this shall we
shito
what the hell
long time no see master sergeant tobiichi and my my fancy bumping into you like this jessica
adeptus two i demand to know why you're attacking us i don't think i'm going to go by that code name
anymore it's no longer needed since i'm quitting d-e-m industries i won't let you betray master westcott
banner gone huh i guess it's not too shabby for something that's brand new
new i'll let you go this time did i stutter that's your cue to turn tails
stop guys step out of it already miku we stop her they'll wake up
okay now you've done it
don't go
it's no use silly
i take it bailey's team failed their objective not that it really matters i anticipated as much
hold on i know you why have you come here what do you want with us
acquired targets toka yatagami and some girl that matches the readings for shito itsuka apprehension
under way
smart move tactically speaking coming from you that means absolutely nothing to me
oh my your attack seems to be less powerful than it used to be
i'll take care of you in no time flat
that's toka come back
oh my god
this afternoon around 5 pm the mysterious disturbance at the side of the tengu festival spread
throughout the city like a wildfire its numbers have swelled to the tens of thousands
damn it
toka
what am i going to do
i'm just so lost
huh
poor shido
you look like someone just walked over your grave
how can i help
you seem like you're in way over your head
come on
come on shido
why don't we have ourselves a little chat
that's fine what about
what about
yoshino and the yamai sisters have been taken from you by a new rogue spirit
and toka has been kidnapped by the wizards from dem
you seem to be heading down a path of absolute despair
i know about everything that's been happening to you my darling
you're not being controlled by her are you
no but sweet of you to ask it's so cute that you think i'm innocent enough to be swayed
by that supposed divas level of supposed performance
hey kurumi i've got a favor to ask
lend me your strength and please help me save toka
well i know why you've come looking for me
but before that please you're the only one i can count on now will you please help me
what a surprising turn of events this has been yes yes i must say it is very unexpected
morning already first i have to open my eyes after i get out of bed i have to wash my face
then i eat breakfast and head off to school with shido
where am i
are you awake it's you please remain calm breaking those bonds wouldn't be advisable in your current
state don't mess with me hurry up and take these off i have to get out of here and save shido we have
operatives searching for shido itsuka as we speak it should be a matter of days before he joins you here
but that's said if he resists too much he may arrive with a broken arm or two
my territory is the most accurate of all the dem wizards any attempt to resist is futile
i'm going to ask you a bunch of questions and i want them answered immediately
hey kurumi why go to miku's place right now no one's home
i mean our time would be better spent trying to save toka
don't worry we'll go save toka but we need to deal with the miku problem first
wow shido take a look at this
oh god look at how humongous it is i could almost fit my whole head in one of these crazy cups
come on what are you doing this is hardly the time you're so serious here take it why don't you try
to put it on too uh no i'm not into that kind of stuff i apologize i must have been mistaken just
thought it would look great on shiori oh you saw that huh that's right i just never had a good
opportunity to see it up close and personal i was hoping maybe you could fix that situation for me hey
would you cut it out already don't be such a wet blanket you only have to wear it for a little while
i really want to see the adorable shiori's angelic face trembling with carnal humiliation stop it
stay back leave her alone leave shiori alone for me it'll be our special secret
that hurt you okay kurumi yes i'm perfectly okay because there was a big brave knight who took the fall
for me no sweat oh no your heart looks like something scratched your cheek huh oh wow that's
weird it's all right though a little spit should clean it right up
what do you think you're doing you said it would be fine with a little spit now didn't you
what's that is something the matter suki no yo imachi well now isn't this interesting look what i found
but isn't that
hey hold on
kurumi
don't worry about me yacht's power is recollection a powerful technique that gives me a special inside
look into some of the target's recent memories memories memories like what like recollections of
a past life reporting on mistress miku have you found that boy yet the gross imposter yes mistress
there's no mistaking it that is so lame oh is that the case he was more elusive than i'd expected
well who finally tracked the pervert down then i hope it's a pretty young lady so i can dote on
her lovingly but if it was a man oh i guess you can give him a piece of candy and send him on his
way he uh got found by like a whole crowd of people it's hard to pick just one person to reward
that is so so lame
he's outside like he just showed up facing her head on is crazy no matter how you slice it even if you
thought of a more certain way to get you sent straight to miku it's too late because we're
already here which means at this point your energy is better spent figuring out how to persuade her
okay fine i guess you're right i've had all these people out searching for you instead you come to me
on your own you must have a great deal of confidence in yourself shiori or should i say
she don't eat
Thank you.
振り払い君の手を握る
今だって夢だって剣を手に
君のこと見つけるよ闇を裂いて
倒れたって不安くたって負けないから
この手をギュッと捕まえて
消えない勇気の炎が
都会照らしている
今だって夢だってみて
Music
You